Aniruddha Mysore, Web Developer, Student, Entrepreneur

aniruddha.mysore@gmail.com | Bangalore, India

https://github.com/animysore74 | https://linkedin.com/in/animysore | http://thenewcon.com

SUMMARY

I am a student pursuing an undergraduate degree in PESIT Bangalore, majoring in Computer Science and Engineering. I am a regular contributor to the open source movement (See Github). I have 3 years experience in Front-End Web Development and am also experienced in Back-End frameworks like Wordpress and am comfortable with PHP and NodeJS. I am a fan of Jekyll and similar Static Site frameworks.

EXPERIENCE

Reap Benefit, Intern

Aug 2016 — Present

http://www.reapbenefit.org/

• Responsibilities include: Building a smart water flow monitor for domestic use Building a pothole-detector app (Working on the Backend) Visualizations of Air Quality Data

KHMD, Web Developer and Graphic Designer

Sept 2015 — Nov 2015

https://khmd.github.io/interface

 Developed the website for KHMD's annual event, Interface and also worked with graphic design. Utilized modern web-technologies like embeded-SVG's to maintain design uniformity across digital and print media and attain interactivity without client-side scripting.

Arcsracing, Brand Manager and Tech Lead

Apr 2015 — Jun 2015

http://arcsracing.com

- Worked to creating a strong online presence for Arcsracing and managed advertising campaigns.
- Organised the Amateur Racing Challenge 2015, a Karting Challenge for amateur racers, allowing them to exhibit their karting skills and passion for motorsport. Responsibilities included Event Branding, developing the website, and managing social media presence.

Beebom, Content Developer

Mar 2015 — May 2015

http://beebom.com

• My responsibilities were Tech Journalism and Reporting. Published list-oriented posts, and articles on latest trends in technology.

Quicksilver Studios, CEO and Founder

Feb 2014 — Dec 2014

http://qs.thenewcon.com

Started and successfully managed my own Web Design company, Quicksilver Studios.
Developed websites and content for clients such as Candyship, a Smart-School vendor based in Bangalore.

AWARDS

Earthian, Wipro

Nov 2013

• Water and Sustainability was the core issue of the Wipro Earthian Awards 2013. My Team performed a water audit of our school. Our final paper was shortlisted at the national level.

Duke of Edinburgh's International Award - Silver, Duke of Edinburgh

Aug 2014

EDUCATION

PES Institute of Technology, Bangalore

2016 — 2020

Undergraduate - College

• Computer Science and Engineeting

Codecademy.com

MOOC -

o HTML/CSS

Javascript